MAURITZ MAJELYNE

MAURITZ.MAJELYNE@HOTMAIL.COM 347-421-3454

Cybersecurity Professional. Able to design and implement disaster recovery plans, map out network topologies, and aid in hardening systems to protect them against possible threats and malware. Has experience using software such as Kibana, Wireshark and Security to monitor and analyze logs, data, and network traffic to spot potential threats. Skilled at resolving hardware/software connectivity issues and setting up firewalls and backup systems. Known as attentive listener, fast learner and highly coachable. Trilingual English/ Dutch/ French. CompTIA A+ and Security + certified

Software: Kali Linux, Ubuntu, Windows Server, Splunk, Metasploit Microsoft Azure, Virtual Box, Wireshark, Kibana, Logstash, Docker IO, Autopsy, Security Onion, Snort, iOS, Android.

Networking Configuration; virtual private network; mapping network drives; Install workgroups, configuring virtual machines and setting up a virtual network (including a load balancer, and firewalls) in a Microsoft Azure environment.

PC Maintenance/Hardware: Operating system installation, Windows Update, system restore, disk cleanup, disk defragmenter, installation of anti-virus, anti-spy-ware software, firewall, filestransfer settings, configuring computers, removing viruses, Trojan, spyware, malware infections. Partitioning and Formatting Hard Drives..

Education

Cybersecurity Bootcamp, Security + Certification, Columbia School of Engineering May 2022 - August 2022

Course Projects:

- Discovered target machines and vulnerable servers on the network using Nmap.
- Exploited vulnerabilities on several target machines and executed a "find the flags" mission.
- Cracked and brute-forced passwords using software such as "John the Ripper" and "Hydra".
- Conducted forensic research and analysis of an iPhone image using Autopsy.

IT Support Training, A+ and Network+ Certifications, Google IT support, Per Scholas.

September 2021- December 2021

Course Projects:

- Disassembled and reassembled a PC, verified its successful boot
- Created a bootable thumb drive using various platforms such as PowerISO and Rufus
- Tested wall outlets using a multimeter and ensuring the outlet output the correct voltages
- Configured a Linksys router adjusting SSID and enabling the WPA2 security protocol

Professional Experience

Compulink May 2022 - Current

IT Support Specialist/contractor/consultant

- Image and deploy approx. 334 workstations with Windows 10 for the NYC DODC using PXE boot.
- Deploy and set up workstations, CAD workstations, monitors, and peripherals around the office.
- Ensure all workstations are properly connected to the Active Directory Domain.

MAURITZ MAJELYNE

MAURITZ.MAJELYNE@HOTMAIL.COM 347-421-3454

Equinox Fitness Oct 2017 - 2022

Member Admin Representative Feb 2020 - September 2021

- Quickly respond to and resolve all member issues, inquiries and concerns in a constructive, efficient and professional manner via phone, chat and email.
- Retain members by determining creative solutions for complex issues and forging strong relationships.
- Support club management and foster a positive club environment with all members.

Shop Manager-on-Duty October 2017- Feb 2020

- Create and maintain positive, sale-driven environment that has provided clients with the best shopping experience. Drive incremental business by executing shop events.
- Resolves any client issues in a helpful, efficient and professional manner.